Tufts University Website Collection UA203
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Website Collection
2009 -- 2021
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Digital Collections and Archives
Tufts University
UA203
790 Web sites
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Tufts University web crawls and Student organizations web crawls.
Scope and Contents
This collection represents web crawls of Tufts University websites and student organization websites conducted, under contract, by the Internet Archives using their tool Archive-It. The first focused crawl was conducted on November 2, 2009. The web crawls are managed directly in Archive-It. Beginning in 2015, student organization websites were added to the crawls. Only websites of student organizations that are officially recognized by the University are crawled.
Biographical / Historical
Tufts Digital Collections and Archives began crawling Tufts University websites in 2009 to document the University's web presence. Since then, crawling has become increasingly robust and comprehensive, with more websites added to the collection, including those of student organizations.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Tufts University; Student life; Student activities; University Relations; Admissions and Recruitment; Student Activities -- Student Government, Clubs, and Organizations
- Tufts University web crawls, 2009 -- 2020; UA203.001; Tufts University; 164 Web sites
  Scope and Contents
  A collection of 164 websites crawled by DCA to document the presence of Tufts University on the web. The majority of the websites in this series are crawled on a monthly basis.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Archived websites can be viewed online using the Internet Archive's Wayback Machine.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research.
  - Arts, Sciences, & Engineering at Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00005; Tufts University
    Open for research.
  - Bengali Cultural Heritage in the Postcolonial Age, 2013-10-23 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00007; Tufts University
  - Bluehost.com, 2016-03-28 -- 2019-08-02; UA203.001.00075; Tufts University
  - Campus Sustainability Progress Report, 2016-03-31 -- 2020-02-02; UA203.001.00069; Tufts University
  - CEEO: Home, 2012-10-17 -- 2020-02-02; UA203.001.00011
  - Center for Interdisciplinary Studies - Tufts University, 2011-08-17 -- 2019-08-02; UA203.001.00013
  - Center for the Enhancement of Learning and Teaching - Office of the Provost, 2010-07-17 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00012
  - Chief Diversity Officer and Associate Provost - Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President, 2011-07-07 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00021; Tufts University
  - Child & Family WebGuide - a directory of sites on child development, teenager and family issues., 2011-02-17 -- 2017-10-23; UA203.001.00090
  - Climate Change: The Role of the University, 2016-03-23; UA203.001.00103; Tufts University
  - Commencement, 2010-10-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00014; Tufts University
  - Community Relations, 2011-07-07 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00015; Tufts University
  - Computer Science Degree Programs - Bachelors, Masters and PH.D. - School of Engineering - Tufts University, 2012-02-17 -- 2020-02-02; UA203.001.00091
  - Core Facilities, 2010-11-17 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00016; Tufts University
  - Crafts House, 2012-05-17 -- 2017-03-15; UA203.001.00074
  - Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine, Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00087; Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine
  - Dashboard - Confluence, 2015-09-23 -- 2019-08-26; UA203.001.00113; Tufts University
  - Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, 2012-02-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00092
  - Department of Public & Environmental Safety, 2010-07-17 -- 2020-02-02; UA203.001.00056
  - Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2020-02-02; UA203.001.00017
  - Digital Communications, 2010-11-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00089; Tufts University
  - Disorientation Guide, 2011-12, 2016-09-08; UA203.001.00112
  - Distinction Awards, 2011-07-07 -- 2020-02-02; UA203.001.00020; Tufts University
  - Engineering - Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00025; Tufts University
  - Events Calendar - Tufts University, 2009-11-12 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00027; Tufts University
  - Ever Wonder?, 2015-12-17 -- 2019-12-17; UA203.001.00028; Tufts University
  - Feinstein International Center - Feinstein International Center - Confluence, 2010-09-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00114
  - FieldEx | Field Exercise in Peacekeeping and Stability Operations, 2013-06-23 -- 2019-08-02; UA203.001.00093
  - Finance Division at Tufts University, 2016-01-23 -- 2017-03-23; UA203.001.00061; Tufts University
  - The Fletcher School, Graduate School of International Affairs, Tufts University, Graduate School of International Relations, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00030; Tufts University
  - The Fletcher School - News and Media, 2010-06-16 -- 2010-06-17; UA203.001.00008; Tufts University
  - Fletcher Security Review, 2014-12-23 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00094
  - The Fulcrum Institute - Tufts University, 2012-05-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00032
  - Gerald J. and Dorothy R. Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy at Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00048
  - Giving to Tufts, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00100; Tufts University
  - Gordon Institute - Engineering Leaders, 2012-02-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00034
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences at Tufts University, 2009-11-12 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00035; Tufts University
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences at Tufts University, 2015-07-23 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00006; Tufts University
  - Human Resources, 2010-06-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00036; Tufts University
  - InsideTufts, 2009-11-02 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00038; Tufts University
  - International Education and Research, 2010-07-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00033
  - Jonathan M. Tisch College of Citizenship and Public Service, 2010-06-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00001; Tufts University
  - LiAM: Linked Archival Metadata, 2013-09-23 -- 2017-02-03; UA203.001.00060; Tufts University
  - LibGuides at Tufts University, 2013-05-23 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00058; Tufts University
  - New Principal Investigator at Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00045; Tufts University
  - Office of Emergency Management, 2013-04-29 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00022; Tufts University
  - Office of Institutional Research and Evaluation, 2010-12-17 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00039
  - Office of Research Administration at Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00057
  - Office of Sustainability - A resource, catalyst, and advocate for environmental sustainability at Tufts, 2011-07-07 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00068; Tufts University
  - Office of the President at Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00051
  - Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President at Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00053
  - Office of the Trustees, 2011-02-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00071; Tufts University
  - Office of the Vice Provost at Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00088
  - Outreach at Tufts University, 2011-02-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00049; Tufts University
  - Peace and Justice Studies - Tufts University, 2010-10-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00050; Tufts University
  - Presidential Search - Tufts University, 2010-12-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00052; Tufts University
  - Provost Search, 2012-10-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00054; Tufts University
  - Rohr Chabad House serving Tufts University, 2010-12-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00096
  - Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences at Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00059
  - The School of Arts and Sciences, Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00004; Tufts University
  - SIS Project | Creating a new Student Information System for Tufts University, 2013-02-16 -- 2017-03-23; UA203.001.00062; Tufts University
  - Spark - Tools for Tufts, 2009-11-09 -- 2017-09-17; UA203.001.00111; Tufts University
  - Spark - Tools for Tufts, 2009-11-12; UA203.001.00009; Tufts University
  - Strategic Planning - Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President, 2012-10-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00066; Tufts University
  - TELD, 2011-09-17 -- 2017-03-23; UA203.001.00064; Tufts University
  - TMCAlums, 2010-12-17 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00098; Tufts University
  - Trek to Talloires, 2011-01-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00070; Tufts University
  - Tufts, 2015-10-09 -- 2020-01-24; UA203.001.00095; Tufts University
  - Tufts Catering, 2011-10-25 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00010; Tufts University
  - Tufts Clinical and Translational Science Institute, 2010-11-17 -- 2018-03-23; UA203.001.00102
  - Tufts Dining Services - Tufts Dining Services - Tufts University, 2009-11-12 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00019; Tufts University
  - Tufts E-News: Daily News. Tufts University's official electronic news source., 2010-06-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00023; Tufts University
  - Tufts Environmental Literacy Institute 2014, 2014-05-23 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00063
  - Tufts – Feinstein International Center | Strengthening the humanity and dignity of people in crisis through knowledge and practice, 2015-09-23 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00029
  - Tufts Global Leadership, 2010-09-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00104
  - TUFTS IN THE WORLD - INDIA 2005, 2014-07-25; UA203.001.00037; Tufts University
  - TUFTS IN THE WORLD - MEXICO 2004, 2014-07-25; UA203.001.00044; Tufts University
  - Tufts in the World – Turkey, 2014-07-25; UA203.001.00081; Tufts University
  - Tufts Institute of the Environment, 2009-11-12 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00026
  - Tufts Journal, 2009-11-09 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00078
  - Tufts Maker Network, 2017-03-17 -- 2020-01-17; UA203.001.00110
  - Tufts Marathon Training, 2010-10-17 -- 2015-12-23; UA203.001.00105
  - Tufts Mountain Club. Go outside., 2010-12-17 -- 2015-11-23; UA203.001.00106
  - Tufts Now, 2010-06-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00046; Tufts University
  - Tufts Now, 2011-02-17 -- 2020-02-06; UA203.001.00047; Tufts University
  - Tufts Observer, 2011-02-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00079
  - Tufts Peer Health Collaborative - PHC Home Page, 2015-09-23 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00077
  - Tufts Student Resources, 2010-10-17 -- 2019-08-02; UA203.001.00107
  - Tufts Student Services, 2015-09-18 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00067; Tufts University
  - Tufts Supports Japan, 2011-04-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00076; Tufts University
  - Tufts - Task Force on the Undergraduate Experience, 2010-09-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00082; Tufts University
  - Tufts Technology Services, 2013-02-16 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00040; Tufts University
  - Tufts University, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00099
  - Tufts University, 2010-11-17 -- 2015-09-18; UA203.001.00065
  - Tufts University Alumni Association, 2010-06-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00072
  - Tufts University Libraries, 2010-06-17 -- 2020-01-17; UA203.001.00097; Tufts University
  - Tufts University Photography, 2015-09-23 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00080
  - Tufts University School of Dental Medicine, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00018; Tufts University
  - Tufts University School of Engineering, 2009-11-09 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00024; Tufts University
  - Tufts University School of Medicine, 2012-04-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00042; Tufts University
  - Tufts University School of Medicine Public Health and Professional Degree Programs, 2012-04-17 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00055
  - Tufts University · Tufts Admissions, 2011-07-07 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00003; Tufts University
  - Tufts University - Undergraduate Education, Student Affairs, & Student Services, 2010-11-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00086; Tufts University
  - Tufts University YouTube channel, 2009-11-12 -- 2010-06-17; UA203.001.00109; Tufts University
  - TuftScope, 2011-02-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00101
    Related Material
    As of December 2015, being crawled in Student Organizations.
  - TuftScope, 2017-09-13 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.001.00073; Tufts University
  - TuftsLife, 2012-05-10 -- 2017-01-23; UA203.001.00115; Tufts University
  - TUSM Development and Alumni Relations, 2010-06-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00041
  - University Information Technology at Tufts University, 2009-11-09 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00083; Tufts University
  - University Relations, 2009-11-12 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00084; Tufts University
  - University Relations, 2010-11-17 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.001.00085; Tufts University
  - World Peace Foundation | Tufts Fletcher School, 2009-11-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.001.00031; Tufts University
  - The Zamboni | Tufts University's Only Intentionally Funny Magazine, 2015-09-17 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.001.00108
  - Access Tufts, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000519; 1 Web sites
  - Brighter World | Tufts Alumni, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000520; 1 Web sites
  - Careers at Tufts, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000521; 1 Web sites
  - CEEO, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000522; 1 Web sites
  - Center for Cognitive Studies: Home, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000523; 1 Web sites
  - Center for Science and Mathematics Teaching, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000524; 1 Web sites
  - Center for South Asian and Indian Ocean Studies, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000525; 1 Web sites
  - Center for the Humanities at Tufts, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000526; 1 Web sites
  - Clinical Nutrition Service at Cummings School – Nutrition information for cats and dogs by board certified nutritionists, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000527; 1 Web sites
  - Continuing Education – at Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000528; 1 Web sites
  - Cummings School Microsites, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000529; 1 Web sites
  - Cummings Veterinary Medical Center, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000530; 1 Web sites
  - Cummings Voices, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000531; 1 Web sites
  - DCA, 2019-08-30; UA203.000532; 1 Web sites
  - Eliot-Pearson Children's School, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000533; 1 Web sites
  - Faculty Profile - Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts University, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000534; 1 Web sites
  - Feinstein International Center, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000535; 1 Web sites
  - Ginn Library, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000536; 1 Web sites
  - GIS@Tufts, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000537; 1 Web sites
  - Global Development and Environment Institute at Tufts University, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000538; 1 Web sites
  - Graduate Programs – Master's and PhD Programs, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000539; 1 Web sites
  - Graduate Programs – Master's and PhD Programs, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000540; 1 Web sites
  - Hirsh Health Sciences Library, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000541; 1 Web sites
  - Institute for Democracy & Higher Education, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000542; 1 Web sites
  - Jonathan M. Tisch College of Civic Life, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000543; 1 Web sites
  - News Center at Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts University, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000544; 1 Web sites
  - Office of the Executive Vice President, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000545; 1 Web sites
  - Operations Division, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000546; 1 Web sites
  - Selected Patient Information Resources in Asian Languages (SPIRAL), 2019-11-12 -- 2019-11-13; UA203.000547; 1 Web sites
  - Selected Programs | Institute for Global Leadership, 2018-08-01; UA203.000548; 1 Web sites
  - TERC - Biomedical Engineering, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000550; 1 Web sites
  - The Fares Center – for Eastern Mediterranean Studies at The Fletcher School at Tufts University, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000551; 1 Web sites
  - The Fletcher Forum of World Affairs, 2020-01-30; UA203.000552; 1 Web sites
  - The Talloires Network, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000553; 1 Web sites
  - Tisch Library website, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000554; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Alumni, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000555; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Center for Scientific Visualization, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000556; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Center for the Study of Drug Development, 2017-05-11 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000557; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Clinical and Translational Science Institute, 2017-08-02 -- 2018-03-23; UA203.000558; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Community Union, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-12-23; UA203.000559; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Health Care Institute, 2017-08-02 -- 2018-03-23; UA203.000560; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Institute of Cosmology, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000561; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Magazine, 2019-07-30 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000562; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Medical Center | Boston Hospital and Academic Medical Center, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000563; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University - Advanced Technology Laboratory, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000564; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Center for Reading and Language Research, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000565; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University European Center in Talloires, France, 2017-08-02 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000566; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Veterinary Emergency Treatment & Specialties, 2018-07-31 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000567; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Wildlife Clinic – at Cummings Veterinary Medical Center, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000568; 1 Web sites
  - Vet School - Alumni, 2019-02-22 -- 2020-01-23; UA203.000569; 1 Web sites
- Student organizations web crawls, 2011 -- 2021; UA203.002; 575 Web sites
  A collection of 349 websites crawled by DCA to document the presence of Tufts University student organizations on the web. The majority of the websites in this series are crawled on a quarterly basis.
  - 180 Degrees Consulting - Tufts, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000119
    General
    Frequency: quarterly crawl. (Inactive)
  - 180 Degrees Consulting - Tufts - Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000378
  - Action for Sexual Assault Prevention @ Tufts, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000121
    Frequency: quarterly crawl.
  - Active Minds at Tufts, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000122
  - American Institute of Chemical Engineers - Tufts University Student Chapter, 2009-11-09 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.000123
  - Anchord - Tufts Christian A Cappella, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000124
  - Anchord - Tufts Christian A Cappella - Twitter, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000125
  - Another Option at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000126
  - AOII - Delta Chapter, 2017 -- 2020; UA203.000127
  - Applejam Productions, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000128
  - Army ROTC @ MIT, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000129
  - Asian American Alliance, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000130
    Frequency: one-time crawl.
  - Association for Women in Mathematics Student Chapter, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000131
  - Association of Latin American Students, 2018 -- 2020; UA203.000132
  - Association of Multiracial People at Tufts, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000133
  - ATO of Massachusetts, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000134
  - Balance Your Life, 2015 -- 2019; UA203.000135
  - Beta Mu of Delta Tau Delta, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000136
  - Biology Union of Graduate Students, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000137
  - BlackOut - Tufts University All Male Step Team, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000138
  - BlackOut Step Team - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000139
  - Caribbean Club - Home, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000140; Tufts Carribean Club
  - CEE Grad Student Advisory Council, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000141
  - Chi Chapter Nupes - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000142
  - Chi Omega, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000143
  - Chi Omega at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000144
  - Concert Board - Tufts University Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000145
  - Consent Culture Network Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2016 April 11; UA203.000146
  - Crafts House, 2012 -- 2017; UA203.000118
    For crawls relating to the Crafts House after March 2017, see the maker.tufts.edu crawl in the Tufts University collection.
  - Eco-Representatives, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000147
  - Emergency Medical Services, 2011 -- 2015; UA203.000148
  - Engineering Student Council, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000149
  - Entertainment Board - Tufts University Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000150
  - ENVY Tufts All-Female Step Team - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000151
  - Eta Sigma Phi, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000152
  - Fraternity and Sorority Life, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000153; Office of Student Life
  - Freshman Class Council - Tufts University Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000154
  - Futurism Society at Tufts, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000155
  - Generation Citizen, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000156
  - Global China Connection, Tufts University Chapter, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000157
  - GlobeMed at Tufts University, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000158
  - Air Force ROTC Det. 365, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000159
  - Imaginet | The Tufts Marketing and Advertising Club, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000160
  - Indian Society At Tufts, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000161
  - J Street U Tufts, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000162
  - Junior Class Council - Tufts University Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000163
  - Kappa - Tufts University, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000164
  - Kappa Alpha Theta at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000165
  - LIFT – National, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000166
  - Love146Tufts | For the abolition of child sex slavery. Nothing less., 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000167
  - Major: Undecided, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000168
  - Media Advocacy Board at Tufts University, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000169
  - Midnight (at Tufts), 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000170
  - MIT Navy ROTC, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000171
  - Muslim Student's Association, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000172
  - National Society of Black Engineers - Tufts Chapter, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000173
  - Non-denominational Christian Fellowship, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000174
  - Not Your Mothers Monologues, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000175
  - Not Your Mother's Monologues - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000176
  - Nu Chapter - Latinas Promoviendo Comunidad, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000177; Nu Chapter of Latinas Promoviendo Comunidad/ Lambda Pi Chi Sorority, Inc.
  - Organization of Graduate Students in Mathematics, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000178
  - Pi Rho Omega, 2017 -- 2019; UA203.000179
  - Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000180
  - Project Linus at Tufts University, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000181
  - Protestant Student Association, 2015-12-09 - 2017-03-11; UA203.000182
  - Public Health at Tufts, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000183
  - Pulse, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000184
  - Quest Scholars, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000185
  - Relay for Life of Tufts University, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000186
  - Returning Students Organization, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000187
  - Sarabande Dance Ensemble, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000188
  - School of Engineering Student Chapter, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000189
  - Senior Class Council - Tufts University Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000190
  - S-Factor A Capella, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000191
  - Sharewood Project, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000192
  - Shir Appeal, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000193
  - Sino-U.S Relations Group Engagement - Tufts SURGE, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000194
  - Sophomore Class Council - Tufts University Programming Board, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000195
  - Spirit of Color, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000196
  - Spoken Word Alliance At Tufts, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000197
  - Spoken Word Alliance At Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000198
  - Strong Women Strong Girls, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000199